混乱之子 前情提要
Previously on Sons of Anarchy...
Tara要和我离婚？还要带走孩子？
Is Tara divorcing me? And taking my sons?
是的
Yes.
怀孕的事....是一个谎言吗？
The pregnancy...was it a lie?
Tara只是想....
- Tara was just trying...
滚出去
- Get out!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你没有感觉到对不起
You are not sorry!
知道为什么 你没资格当一个母亲吗？
Do you know why you're not capable of being a mother?
因为你是一个胆小鬼
Because you're a coward.
什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
意思就是 你是个愚蠢 懦弱的吸毒鬼
It means you're a stupid, weak junkie.
Gaalan给我开出的条件是
Gaalan let me know that the offer for me to be the
让我继续做他们的经销商
distributor's still on the table.
他们想把我劫出去
They want to spring me out of here.
两周后 劫持送我去庭审的囚车
Take down the transports bringing me to my hearing in two weeks.
Clay的庭审被提前了
Clay's trial has been moved up.
他们明天就把他转送出去
They transport him tomorrow.
计划有麻烦了 我们需要一些援手
Complicates our plan.Gonna need some help.
我们不会参与劫持囚车
We're not part of taking down that transport.
我们大家都需要这事能成
We both need this to happen.
让我们的枪支生意继续推进 让你们全身而退
Moves guns forward for us, puts 'em behind you.
我来这儿和你谈谈条件
I'm here to make you an offer.
Gaalan O'Shay 我会把他交给你 还有一大船枪械 绝不含糊
Gaalan O'Shay. I will deliver him with a shipment of guns, open and shut.
你想得到什么好处？
What's in it for you?
豁免俱乐部所有关于枪支的指控
Immunity for the MC for all gun charges.
Wendy!
她似乎想自己戒毒
Looks like she was trying to get herself in rehab.
Wayne 帮她收拾一个包裹
Wayne, pack her a bag.
我们去哪？
Where are we going?
回家 亲爱的
Home, sweetheart.
我想要你那笔交易
- I want your deal.
很遗憾
- I'm sorry.
那笔交易已经不存在了
That deal's no longer on the table.
有些其他的事情待定
There are other things pending.
如果担心你和孩子们的安全
If you fear for the safety of you and your boys...
我可以帮忙
I can help.
不 你不能
No, you can't.
嗨 小家伙
Hey, you.
早上好
Good morning.
嗯
Yeah.
让我们来看看Abel吧
Yeah. Should we go check on Abel
来看看Abel
Let's go check on Abel.
他在哪？
Where is he?
工作
Work.
你能在外面等着吗 我好给孩子喂点吃的
Could you please wait outside so I can feed my son?
当然
Sure.
当我把孩子放在日托所 你们派谁来看着？
When I drop them off at day care, who do you watch then?
你
You.
但是不用去日托所了
But no day care.
Jax希望 再把他们放在圣托玛斯医院了
Jax doesn't want them at St. Thomas anymore.
这个是豁免协议
This is the immunity agreement.
包含俱乐部的所有人或与俱乐部有关的人
It covers everyone in or associated with the MC.
还有关于Tara的协议 正如我答应过的
And Tara's deal. As promised.
不用进监狱服刑
No jail time.
现在 他们都已经签字批准了
Now, they're both signed and approved.
直到你把Gaalan O'Shay和枪支交给我们才会执行
They don't get executed until you
deliver Gaalan O'Shay and the guns.
在西端码头那 有一个维修仓库
There's an old maintenance
warehouse out on the west end docks.
叫Kilmer Pier 几年前被关闭了
Kilmer Pier. They closed it down a few years back.
我知道那里
I know it.
情况是这样的
That's the drop.
Gaalan带着那批货 在中午11点到1点左右到那
Gaalan will be there with the guns sometime between 11:00 and 1:00.
有多少人？
With how many people?
10个 也许12个
Ten, maybe a dozen guys.
他们很谨慎 并且全副武装
They're gonna be cautious and very well armed.
好的
Okay.
完事了我们再谈
We'll talk after it's done.
你把这事交给州警办？
You handle this with the sheriffs?
还是把联邦调查局的人搬过来？
Or you bring in Feds and local?
这你就不用操心
That's none of your concern.
那样有用吗？
Think that helped?
我不知道
I don't know.
至少我们尝试过了
Least I'll know I tried.
是啊 确实
Yeah, you did.
她怎样了？
How's she doing?
她现在睡着了
Well, she's asleep now.
你在帮她做这一切？
You know, all this stuff you're doing for her?
很好 很好
Great. Great.
娃他妈
Mama?
Wendy必须靠自己戒毒
Wendy's got to get herself into a rehab.
我知道
I know.
一会我打几个电话
I'll make the calls.
我们以前关系不太好 我和她
We have rough history, me and her.
我只是想去帮帮她 而不是害她
I was just trying to help her more than hurt her.
嗯
Mm.
作为一种改变吧
For a change.
嗨 你认为这种宽容是否
Hey, you think any of this mercy might ever be able
也能用到Tara身上？
to spill over into Tara's cup?
她可是你亲孙子的老妈 Gem
She's the mother of your grandson, Gem.
这种关系永远都改变不了的
Come on, that shit ain't never gonna change.
我做不到
I can't go there.
哦 明白 那种深深的....
Oh. See, that deep...
我理解 嗯
I get it, uh-huh.
我明白那种感觉
I know it.
我的前妻--那婆娘在她怀孕的时候一直注射毒品
My ex-- that bitch was shooting
junk the whole time she was pregnant.
导致Lucius一辈子的痛苦
And the pain that Lucius has to live with...
都是她造成的
that's on her. Okay?
我..我对她咬牙切齿
and I-I can chew that hate that I feel for her.
她死了
She's dead.
你没有
You're not.
是啊 但是我还得承受这种痛苦
Yeah, but I-I'm the one that's
still got to live with all that shit.
都是因为在她活着的时候 我做得不够好
'Cause I never made it right when she was alive.
我不能原谅她 Nero
I can't forgive her, Nero.
至少现在不行
Not now.
好吧
Okay.
孤独地骑行在这尘世
Riding through this world  all alone
上帝将灵魂带走
God takes your soul
徒剩躯壳
You're on your own
如乌鸦掠过天际
The crow flies straight
直飞远方
a perfect line
缠绵在恶魔之床
on the devil's bed
直至死亡
until you die
才将这一世的轨迹
Gotta look this life
看个端详
in the eye
混乱之子 第六季 第十一集
英文字幕：n17t01 翻译：Wilsonyy 校对：Dena
T 叔叔
- Uncle T!
嗨
- Hey!
你好啊 小捣蛋
Hey there, you little monster.
嗨
Hey.
呃 我得去见我的新律师
Um, I have to go meet my new lawyer.
不介意照看一会吧？
Would you mind watching them for a bit?
很明显 我不准把他们再放到日托所了
Apparently, I'm not allowed to take them to day care anymore.
当然不介意
Yeah. Of course.
哦 小家伙
Oh, boy...
你越来越沉了
you're getting heavy.
Gemma在哪？
Where's Gemma?
呃...她还没来
Uh... she ain't here yet.
好吧
Okay.
有劳你了
Thank you.
来吧 小朋友
Come with me, big boy.
喂 Tara
Uh, Tara...
很遗憾 发生这么多糟糕的事
I'm sorry the way all this went down.
我知道你是好意的
I know your heart was in the right place.
遗憾的是 我的好意没人在乎
Unfortunately, where my heart is matters very little.
她看上去很难过
She seems really sad.
确实有很多难过的事
Lot of that going around.
很难有转机了 不是吗？
It's not gonna get any better, is it?
今天肯定不行 Chucky
Not today, Chucky.
Lowen把情况都告诉了我 不管是正式的还是非正式的
Lowen brought me up to speed on
everything, both on and off the record.
很好
Good.
如果还有什么....呃...她不知道的
If there is anything that, uh...maybe she didn't
最好现在告诉我
know about, now would be a good time to tell me.
没有
No.
好吧
Okay.
我正在进行离婚和监护人的文字工作
I'm prepared to execute the divorce and custody paperwork,
但是你要知道这其中的风险 Knowles医生
but you need to understand the risk here, Dr. Knowles.
这些关于你丈夫的材料？
These transcripts about your husband?
如果我们利用这些材料来争取你孩子的监护权
If we use them to get custody of your boys,
他将有权告诉他的律师
he'll have the right to tell his side of it.
让它成为公开资料
Makes it public record.
而地方检察官就可以在Pamela Toric的案子上加以利用
The DA can use that in the Pamela Toric trial.
那会产生什么后果？
And what does that do?
我们最大的优势是信誉
The biggest part of our defense is your credibility.
如果地方检察官发现流产的事情有可疑之处
If the DA finds out about the doubts regarding the
他们会努力发掘真相
miscarriage, they'll dig in to get the truth.
如果他们发现什么对我们不利的....
If what they find comes back unfavorable...
我们就输了
I lose my defense.
那么说 我不得不做个选择
So I have to choose?
要孩子还是要自由？
My boys or my freedom?
这两样都不能确保
There's no guarantee of either.
但是 基本上 是的 这就是现实
But essentially, yes,I guess that's true.
先生们
Gentlemen.
这些是为我们准备的？
These for us?
是的
Aye.
只是为了确保不被人查到
Just making sure they're untraceable.
只要确保能开动就行
Just make sure they run.
当然 把油箱都加满了
They do. Even filled the tanks.
Tig 检查一下
Tig, check 'em.
行 没问题
Yeah, you got it.
West Quinn 跟我来
West, Quinn, come on.
Gaalan在哪？
Where's Gaalan?
他会在机库和我们碰头
He's meeting us at the hangar.
那里就是我们为Clay储存了枪支的地方
That's where we're storing the guns for Clay.
Gaalan和货一起？
Gaalan bringing the shipment with him?
搞定之后 我和Hugh去放货的地方
After the takedown, me and Hugh will go to the barn,
把货拿上 我们再到机库碰面
we'll pick it up, we'll meet you at the hangar.
这就是你的帮手吗？
Is he all you got?
我能对付
I'm all you need.
我们让Neil在监狱外面望风
We got Neil positioned outside the prison.
他是我们了解路上情况的耳目
He's our eyes on the road.
那么 我们该怎样行动？
So, how we doing this?
我来详细给你们解释一下
I'll walk you through it.
叫上Tig
Get Tig.
Tiggy!
待着
Stay.
各位 去帮帮忙
You guys, go help 'em out.
我们了解了路线、人员和运输车辆的情况
We know the route,the crew and the trucks.
行动将会简单 干净 利落
It'll be clean, fast and easy.
我们需要用到50口径的家伙？
We're going to need .50-cals?
我们必须要打穿防弹玻璃
We'll be having to smash through some bulletproof glass.
这算是简单利落吗？
Is that the fast or the easy part?
我以前干过 小伙子
I've done this before, lads.
你经历过吧？
- You have?
是啊
- Aye.
两次
Twice.
在Armagh的地方监狱
Local cage in Armagh.
你把Harper弄出来 什么地方来着？--Magilligan
And you sprung Harper from--where was it?-- Magilligan.
是的
Aye.
大约一个小时后 Clay就会被押上车
Clay will be loading up in about an hour.
押送车队将会行经西区前往Fremont
His transport will run through the east end, on to Fremont.
Neil将会确认他们出发的时间
Neil will confirm when he leaves.
Clay会被关在一个铁质车厢里 前后都有押送车辆
Clay will be in an iron wagon,with a lead and follow car.
有6-8个人 全副武装
Six to eight men.Heavily armed.
我们分别乘坐4俩货车
We're in four different delivery trucks.
不同颜色 不同分工
Different colors,different jobs.
每量车配两人
Two men in each.
这是A点 进入Fremont的必经之路
Point A is here, access road off of Fremont.
我们停下来等着
We park and we wait.
有很多车来来往往 所以不会引起别人注意
Lots of trucks are coming and going,
so it'll look like business as usual.
一旦接到目标靠近的电话
When we get the call on the approach,
我们就从这儿的B点进入Fremont
we enter Fremont at point B here.
我们需要交通很顺畅
We'll have a clear sight line of the traffic--
南面和北面都如此
both north, south wide open.
你们明白了吗？
You got it?
我们出发
Let's go.
大概一个小时以后 你们就回修理厂
Give it an hour or so, then head back to TM.
没问题 兄弟
You got it, brother.
是的 我们会好好招待他们一番
Yeah, we'll keep 'em entertained.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
是的
Yeah.
准备好了
Ready.
为什么我们是粉色的车？
Why are we pink?
行了 Tiggy 你喜欢粉色
Come on, Tiggy.You love pink.
行了 发现他们四个人
All right.We got four of them.
Teller不在这 但是我认识其中两个
Teller's not there, but I recognize two of them.
是混乱之子的人
It's SAMCRO.
看来没错
Looks like it's real.
各单位注意 确认行动
All units,we have confirmation.
原地待命 完毕
Stand by. Over.
这帮爱尔兰人不会乖乖的束手就擒
The Irish aren't going to go down without a fight.
我们有3个战术分队准备包围他们
We've got three tacticals ready to close in.
要是他们负隅顽抗 就太蠢了
They resist, they're fools.
你认为行动会不妙？
How do you think this goes down?
40个州警 十来个爱尔兰战士 很多的枪
40 sheriffs, dozen Irish soldiers, lots of guns.
要想不妙都很难
Only one way it can go down.
瞧瞧我的乖孩子
Look at my hard-working boys.
Tara在处理律师的事
Tara had a lawyer thing.
嗯 我知道 Rat给我打了电话
Yeah, I know.Rat called me.
Miller.
Wendy怎样了？
How's Wendy?
啊 她可是遭罪了
Ah, she's hurting.
Nero在照看她
Nero's keeping an eye on her.
我在想 要不把孩子接过去
I'm thinking I'm going to take the boys over there.
让她看看Abel 可能对她比较好
Might do her some good to see Abel.
可是不确定是否对Abel有益
Not sure how good it will do Abel.
嗨
Hey.
他将来迟早会知道 谁是他的亲生妈妈
He's going to find out sooner or later who his mom really is.
他也一样
So is he.
是啊
Yeah.
确实是这样
I guess that's true.
我帮Tara的事...
Me helping Tara--
你应该知道 都是为了他们
you do know it was all about them.
我明白
I know.
这仍然是个大问题
Which is still the case.
要是Tara一走了之 那就出大麻烦了
If Tara gets off, all this shit that's gone down,
但是她还是他们的妈妈
she's still their mom.
你认为如何？
What does that look like?
那要Jax做决定
That's Jax's call.
如果真的要她离开 他俩怎么办？
And if she goes away,what happens to them?
别说那些俱乐部或者大家庭之类的废话
And don't give me all that club and family rhetoric.
我说的是 长此以往怎么办 Gemma
I'm talking about the day-to-day of it, Gemma.
谁来照顾他们？
Who takes care of them?
我来
I do.
真的？
Really?
你觉得你能胜任吗？
You think you're up to that?
你是说我太老了？
You saying I'm too old?
我是说一个奶奶和一个妈妈的角色是不同的
I'm saying being a grandma and-and
being a mom are two different jobs.
我知道责任重大 Wayne
I'm aware of the burden, Wayne.
来吧 宝贝
Come here, baby.
好了 小宝贝
There we go.
对于那些人的责任呢？
What about the burden on them?
我是说Opie、半袋、Phil
Opie, Half-Sack, Phil--
他们也是别人的儿子
they were all somebody's sons.
假如他们的妈妈有机会重来一次
If their mothers had a chance to do it over again,
引导他们走向不同的方向
lead them in a different direction...
这世上没后悔药可吃 Wayne
There are no second chances, Wayne.
我们只有一次机会 去爱孩子 把他们养大成人
We get one shot at loving and raising our kids.
我会把这事干好
And I'm going to do this right.
我不怀疑你能把孩子们养大
I have no doubt that you could raise these boys.
我知道你很爱他们
I know how much you love them.
但是你必须意识到 现在不是1967年的那个时候了 亲爱的
But you got to realize this isn't 1967 anymore, sweetheart.
现在的世界 不再罗曼蒂克或者崇尚自由
This life, it ain't romantic or free.
很多事情变得不可理喻
There's no path to anything that makes any sense.
这世道肮脏而悲惨
It's just dirty and sad.
我们都心知肚明 情况会变得更糟
And we both know it's only going to get worse.
我去接Abel
I'm going to get Abel.
嗨
Hey.
如果你真的不想让孩子们呆在这
If you really don't want these boys here,
为什么你还要帮我？
why are you still helping me?
我发现我仍然待在这 原因就是一样的
For the same reason I find myself still here,
不管多混乱或是多大伤害
no matter what the upset or damage.
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
我深深得爱着你
I'm in love with you.
嗨
Hey.
Juice.
你还在状态吧？
You here?
当然
Yeah.
我还没崩溃 兄弟
I'm not having a breakdown, man.
我想你不会
I didn't think you were.
Chibs还有一些其他的弟兄 我知道他们很担心
Chibs and some of the other guys, I know they're worried.
他们不应该担心吗？
Should they be?
不应该
No.
可能只是感觉不同吧
Just feels different.
我感觉就不同
I feel different.
是啊
Yeah.
我明白了
I get that.
我就觉得 我们在做正确的事情 Jax
I got to feel like I'm doing something right, Jax.
不是那种“对或错”的对，不过....
Not like "right or wrong" kind of right, but...
我感觉自己似乎是....
I got to feel like I'm... I'm...
似乎是一个好人
Like you're one of the good guys.
是的
Yeah.
以前我知道 我是
I used to know how to find some of that.
现在你还是可以
You still can.
喂
Yeah.
Neil打来电话
Neil called.
只有一辆押送车 总共5个人 行了 我们行动
Only one chaser, five total.Come on, let's go.
好的
Okay.
是Connor打来的 他们上路了
That was Connor.They're en route.
只有一辆车押送 有5个人
Transport, only one follow vehicle, five guys.
好的
Cool.
我们出发
Here we go.
这件事情完了之后 兄弟 我们都成了守法公民 没有污点了
After this, brother, it's all white hats and tight pussy.
好的
Yeah.
他们在那 后面跟着囚车
There they are.Following the transport.
我们动手 来吧 宝贝 动手
Let's do this. Come on, baby.Let's do it.
我突然觉得需要加速
I suddenly feel the need for speed.
动手
Do it!
天呐 他们被撞了 调度中心 代号3
Holy shit! They got hit! Dispatch, Code Three!
我们的跟送车发生了碰撞
Our follow vehicle has been in a collision.
发生了紧急情况
We have an 11-99 in progress.
需要立即支援 有警官受伤了
Requesting immediate backup.Officers down.
他们还有呼吸 Connor来了
They're still breathing.Here's Connor.
我们走 我们走
Let's go, let's go.
赶紧撤 赶紧
Let's move it, move it.
老天 有埋伏 我们他妈的该怎么办？
Holy shit. It's an ambush.What in the hell do we do?
需要我的建议吗？
You want my advice?
闭嘴 混蛋
Shut up, asshole!
遵照规则办 Jenkins 快开车
Follow protocol,Jenkins, and drive!
关上门
Got the door!
我们走 快走 快走
Let's move it!Go, go, go, go, go!
抓紧 兄弟
Hold on, brother.
糟了 这里是编号 Sierra-4-0押送车
Shit! This is Sierra-4-0.
我们遭到袭击 所有单位注意
We are under attack. This is an all-units call!
全部人员向我增援
We need everybody at our 20 now!
放他出来 不会有人受伤
Let him out!No one gets hurt!
天杀的他们到底是什么人 Morrow
Who the hell are they, Morrow?
公平的上帝派来的天使
Angels sent by the god of justice.
好吧 我告诉你一个好消息 笨蛋
Well, I got news for you, shithead.
这玩意是防弹的
This thing's a tank.
把枪放在引擎盖上 马上
Put the guns on the hood now!
打开门
Open the door!
把钥匙交出来
Give me the keys now!
给
Here.
拿着
Take it.
下车 下车
Get out, get out.
好吧 好吧 我出来
All right, all right, I'm out.
爱尔兰人死哪去了？
Where the hell are the Irish?
当然在爱尔兰
In Ireland.
他们要离开了
All right, they're leaving!
是混乱之子的人--他们要离开了--空着手
The MC-- they're headed out empty-handed!
我们刚收到一个全体增援的请求
We just got an all-units request.
有人在Fremont东面劫持了囚车
Someone's taking down a prisoner transport on East Fremont.
囚犯是谁？
Who's the prisoner?
Clay Morrow.
调虎离山之计
Pulling all our resources to the other side of town.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
是啊
Yeah.
好了 我们走 快点 走了
All right, let's go.Come on, move!
快点
Come on!
赶紧 走了 快快 我们走
Back it up, move it!Come on, let's go!
妈的
Shit!
Hayes!
惨了
Shit.
有多糟？
How bad is it?
防弹背心挡了一颗 但是他的肩膀伤得很重
Well, the vest took one, but his shoulder's bad.
我可应付不了 兄弟
This is way beyond me, brother.
你没事吧？
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
Clay 把囚服换掉
Clay, wardrobe upgrade.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
那个警察会一直开枪
That cop was gonna keep shooting.
我知道 赶紧开到停机场
I know. Just head to the airstrip.
不 现在你不能靠近炉子
No, you can't get that close to the stove right now.
你必须要当心点
You have to be careful.
谁在敲门？
Who's at the door?
嗨
- Hey.
- Hi.
妈咪
- Mommy!
哦 嗨 你在干嘛呢 小家伙？
Oh, hey! What you doing there, buddy?
在为Wendy做午餐 她生病了
Making lunch for Wendy.She's sick.
你真好
That's nice of you.
Abel 也许你长大了会当一个医生
Abel, maybe you're gonna grow up and be
像你妈妈一样
a doctor like your mom someday.
喂
Hello.
是的 她刚进屋 出了什么事
Yeah, she just walked in.What's the matter?
谢谢你们照看他们
Thanks for looking after them.
嗨 我们把鞋穿上 好吗？
Hey, let's put on your shoes, okay?
我们要回家了 小家伙
We're gonna go home now, buddy.
嗨 我帮你拿鞋 来吧
Hey, I'll get your shoes.Come on.
坐上来 就是这样 抬起来
Come up here. That's it, get up here.
我们一起吃午餐吧
You can join us for lunch.
不 谢了
No, thanks.
Wendy来干嘛？
What's Wendy doing here?
戒毒所下周才能接收她
We couldn't get her into rehab until next week,
所以我们得照看着她 一直到那时候
so we're looking out for her until then.
让个医生去看看她 也许是个不错的主意
Might be a good idea for a doctor to take a look at her.
是啊 你们应该去请一个
Yeah, you should get one.
我已经没有执业资格了
I don't have a license to practice.
那没关系
That doesn't matter.
是Jax打来的 她一直在找你
That was Jax; he's been trying to get ahold of you.
来吧 亲爱的
Come here, darling.
我要你去奶奶的房间 把你的新书拿来
I want you to go on and get your new books out of Grandma's room.
给妈咪炫耀一下 去吧
You show Mom. Go on.
Bobby中枪了 很严重
Bobby's been shot. It's bad.
发生什么事？
What happened?
我在路上告诉你
I'll tell you on the way over.
快点 我们得走了
Come on. We gotta go.
怎么...我们就这样假装什么事也没发生过 我再继续当黑帮医生？
So...so, what, we just pretend
nothing happened and I'm mob doctor again?
如果能救他一命 我愿意假装下去
Well, I'm willing to pretend if it's gonna save his life.
Bobby快要死了
Bobby's gonna die.
老天 好吧
Jesus Christ. All right.
我得回趟家 把包带上
I need to go by my house and pick up my bag.
来 我来照看他 来吧
Here, I got him.Come here.
来吧 小家伙 哦
Come on, bub. Oh!
我一会就回来 宝贝
I'll be back in a little bit, baby.
Wayne会照看你们的 好吗？
Wayne's gonna look after you guys, okay?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
嗨
Hey!
我们的...午餐哪去了？
Where's my... where's my lunch?
我还以为你做了通心粉和芝士
I thought you were making macaroni and cheese?
来吧
Come on.
让我们一起动手做
Let's go do this.
收到 他们已经到场
Copy that. They're in position.
货车没有登记过 也没有车辆识别号码
Trucks weren't registered; no VIN numbers.
我们正在寻找现场的目击证人和摄像探头
We're still canvassing the area looking for wits, cameras,
以及一切能找到的东西
anything that we can find.
Jenkins说了什么？
What did Jenkins have to say?
8-10个人 男性 戴着面罩和攻击性武器
Eight to ten masked males, assault weapons.
他们分乘两辆车逃窜
They got away in two trucks.
他们驾车离开时 Hayes开了几枪 打中了其中一个
Hayes got off a few shots into one
of them as they were driving away.
后来被他们撞死了
Before they ran him over.
我们已经留意这片医院的情况
We alerted the hospitals in the area.
你想要我们去围捕帮会吗？
You want me to round up the MC?
时机未到
Not yet.
我得重新评估我的计划
I need to reevaluate my options.
好吧
All right.
情况怎样？
How's it look?
我把血止住了 但还是很糟糕
I stopped the bleeding, but it's bad.
好吧 Tara马上就到
All right, Tara will be here soon.
陪着Bobby
Stay with Bobby.
没问题
You got it.
谢谢你 兄弟
Thank you, brother.
为今天的事情
For today.
他在等你们
He's ready for you.
先生们
Gentlemen.
谢谢你 Gaalan
Thank you, Gaalan.
应该感激的是我 朋友
The gratitude is mine, friend.
我们还有很多事情要合作 你和我
We've a lot of work to do, you and I.
嗯 哼
Mm-hmm.
干的漂亮 Jaxson
Good job, Jackson.
老天
Jesus Christ.
我们投过票
We had a vote.
决定必须必须那样做
Decided this had to happen.
Tara和Gemma来了
Tara and Gemma.
让她们进来
Let them in.
关上门
Shut the door.
这事怎样应付Nero Gemma还有Tara？
How is this gonna play out with Nero, Gemma and Tara?
同样的方法
Same way.
了解一下Connor到达的时间
Get an ETA on Connor.
好的
Aye.
Bobby在车里
Bobby's in the truck.
哦 老天
Oh, Jesus.
我需要人来帮忙
Yeah. I need some help.
Juice.
给Tara搭把手
Help Tara.
行
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
其他人没事吧
Everybody else okay?
嗯
Yeah.
Gemma.
没想到这么快就见面了
Didn't think I'd see you this soon.
我想我很幸运
Guess I'm just lucky.
他们要把你送到贝尔法斯特去？
They carting you off to Belfast?
我想不会
I don't think so.
我还以为计划好了
I thought that was the plan.
我认为有其他计划了
I think there's another plan.
很高心 你并不孤单 Gem
I'm glad you're not alone, Gem.
Gemma告诉你的？
Gemma tell you?
我们就过来了
Coming over.
现在你知道所有的事情 兄弟
Now you know everything, brother.
我倒是希望我不知道
I wish I didn't.
这就是你退出枪支生意的方式？
This your way of getting out of guns?
劫持囚车 杀了警察
Taking down a prison transport, killing a sheriff?
因为这事马上就会闹得满城风雨 兄弟
'Cause this shit is all over the news, mano.
还不止这些
It's more than that.
不止？真的？
More? Really?
我不知道我是否还能承受更多 Jax
I don't know if I could take much more, Jax.
你认为怎样？
What do you think?
很严重 我需要手术工具 碎片的位置很深
It's serious. I need surgical tools.That slug's in deep.
有些玻璃碎片 离血管很近
There's some shards of glass that are really close to the nerve.
我们要让他稳定下来
We have to stabilize him.
我不能....不能在这做手术
I can't... I can't do it here.
我们把他带到小木屋去
- We'll take him to the cabin.
好的
- Okay.
我必须去一趟圣托玛斯医院 拿一些材料和用具
I need to go by St. Thomas and get some supplies.
Connor出来15分钟了
Connor's 15 minutes out.
发生了什么事 帮主？
So, what happens now, Pres?
我们要和爱尔兰和解
We settle with the Irish.
嗯
Hmm.
那么 地上躺着的三具尸体 你怎么和解？
And, uh, how do we do that with three dead bodies?
换你会怎么办？
How would you do it?
嗯   我是说 聪明的计划应该这样
Well... I mean, the smart plan
把这事说成是关系恶化了
would be to blame it on a bad relationship.
两个家伙以前有些过节
You know, two guys with some history get into a beef.
事情一环扣一环
One thing leads to another.
也许起不了什么作用
Couldn't be helped.
听上去不错
Sounds about right.
我猜你们 呃 还有我不知道的投票决定的内容
So, I guess you, uh, had another vote I wasn't privy to.
是的 确实
Yeah, we did.
这次是不记名投票
This time it was unanimous.
说得对
Fair enough.
走吧
Let's go.
这样行了吗？
This good?
是的
Yeah.
你还好吗？
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我要 嗯..送她去
I'll, um... I'll take her to
圣托玛斯医院 取她需要的东西
St. Thomas, get what she needs.
然后送她去小木屋
Take her up to the cabin.
多谢
Thanks.
现在我明白了 你指的“更多”
Now I know what you meant by "More."
我很高兴你能在场
I'm glad you were here.
今天发生的事情 是我们对糟糕的过去 做最后的了结
What went down today was us burying
the last piece of a very broken past.
你我现在一起合作的事情 才是帮会的未来
What you and me are doing
together, that's SAMCRO's future.
回头见
I'll see you up there.
辛苦你了
Thank you.
确定不需要我们在这里了？
You sure you don't need us here?
嗯
No.
把Bobby送到小木屋
Get Bobby up to the cabin.
我会在那和你们碰头
I'll meet you up there.
Connor随时会到 兄弟
Connor will be here any minute, brother.
嗯
Yeah.
Clay的事情....
- That shit with Clay...
事先我不知道
- I didn't know.
他们投票决定的？
They voted that?
是的
Yeah.
几个月之前 Clay杀害了Piney Winston
A few months ago, Clay killed Piney Winston.
帮会的元老之一
One of the original members.
然后他让毒品集团来谋杀我
Then he ordered the cartel to kill me.
因为我知道他对John Teller的所作所为
Because I knew what he did to John Teller.
是Jax阻止了他们 但是 那件事情 导致我的手彻底废了
Jax stopped them, but that's,um, how my hand got crushed.
从而毁了我的职业生涯
Ruined my career.
老天
Jesus.
Clay Morrow早就该死了
Clay Morrow should've been dead a long time ago.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事
It's okay.
我好恨他
I hated him so much.
喂
- Hello.
Dr. Knowles 是我 Thyne Patterson
- Dr. Knowles, Thyne Patterson.
我需要和你谈谈
- I need to speak with you.
谈什么？
- About what?
混乱之子
The Sons of Anarchy.
你能来我的办公室见面吗？
Can you meet me at my office?
呃 不行
Uh, no.
要不到你的办公室 医院里的
Your office then, at the hospital.
好吧
Okay.
我马上就来
I'm on my way.
是jax吗？
- Was that Jax?
不是
- No.
是律师
- Lawyers.
对不起
- Sorry.
我知道那有些...
I know that's probably...
你没事吧？
- You okay?
嗯
- Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗯？
- Yeah?
去吧
- Go.
看上去不错 Jackie
Looks good, Jackie.
好了吗？
Yeah?
来吧 把车停进来
Come on, pull it in here.
停
Stop.
还有人呢？
Where's all your men?
带Bobby包扎去了
Took Bobby to get patched up.
他没事吧？
He gonna make it?
嗯 应该没事
Aye, think so.
Gaalan在办公室里面？
- Gaalan in the office?
是的
- Yeah.
需要帮忙把那些枪卸下来吗？
You, uh, need help unloading the guns?
多谢
- I appreciate it.
嗯 没事
- Yeah, sure.
老天
Mother of Christ.
哦 天啊
Aw, Jesus.
当心点....兄弟
Easy... brother.
我来告诉你怎么回事
Let me tell you what happened here.
Clay 和 Gaalan有些私下的交易
Clay and Gaalan had some kind of side deal.
后来情况恶化 他们开始争执起来
It went bad. They started arguing.
Clay开枪杀了Gaalan
Clay shot Gaalan.
你们的人冲进来
Your men ran in.
Clay也把他们放倒了
Clay dropped them, too.
当他转过来对付我们时 我们别无选择
When he turned on us,we had no choice.
我们把他杀了
We killed him.
天杀的你们到底干了什么？
What the hell did you do?
我们不得已而为之
We did what we had to.
我们干掉了杀害你们的人的家伙
We killed the man that killed your men.
这就是你要告诉爱尔兰之王们的故事
That's what you're gonna tell the Kings.
人都是你杀的？
Did you murder them all?
你没有仔细听我的话
You're not listening to what I'm saying.
我告诉你 你所需要的真实情况
I am giving you the truth you need.
只有这样的说法 才能保住你我的命
The only story that protects both of us.
要是有其他的说法 都是说不过去的
Any other truth, you look like a failure.
Clay原本可以保住我们的枪支生意
Clay was keeping our gun business alive.
仍然会的
That still happens.
你告诉Roarke和其他的人 August Marks是他们
You tell Roarke and the others that August Marks is their
在北加州市场唯一的选择
only option in Northern Cali.
华人帮会将杀入这个市场 如果你们爱尔兰共和军
The Chinese are gonna jump on the
market if the IRA wait to
磨磨蹭蹭找其他的下家的话
find another distributor.
要不你们和黑人帮合作 要不你们满盘皆输
It's work with black or lose it all.
你在玩我 你这杂种 是不是？
You played me, you bastard, didn't you?
就算我在玩你 我也要把你玩到头头的位置
If I did, I played you right into the number one slot.
是去是留 全取决于你
It's up to you whether you want to stay there.
你是一个聪明 正派的人 Connor
You're a smart,decent guy, Connor.
我们都很清楚 这事必然会发生
We both know this had to happen.
要是我们不这么做 躺在地上的将是你我
It was gonna be you and me lying on the floor if it didn't.
他们罪有应得
They earned that blood.
那么 就让我们翻过这一页
So let's move past it.
这样我们都能回家 回到家人身边
So we can both go home to our families.
他们肯定还要听听你们的说法
The Kings will want to know your side of the story.
不管怎样都行
Whatever you need.
要是他们不相信我们怎么办？
And what if they don't believe us then what?
那么我们以圣经的名义发誓
Then we swear on a stack of Catholic bibles.
明早我会给贝尔法斯特那边打电话
I'll call Belfast in the morning.
很好
Good.
我们必须把KG-9与尸体留下
We're going to need to leave the KG-9's here with the bodies.
其他的都带走
Take the rest of the guns.
储存在饮料仓库
Store them in the beverage warehouse.
为什么？
Why?
我需要这些解决一些问题
I need to deal with a local problem.
这些枪我会买单
I'll cover the cost of the guns.
我会尽快回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
这确实一下难以接受 娃他妈 很遗憾
That was rough, mama. I'm sorry.
我不知道为什么 我他妈的这么难过
I don't know why I'm so goddamn sad.
嗨 不管好坏 Clay在你的生活中占了很大一块
Hey, good or bad, Clay was a huge piece of your life.
你知道
You know?
这会需要一段时间适应
It's going to take a minute.
他可不值得我浪费时间
He's not worth a minute.
好吧
Okay.
你要在俱乐部扮演什么角色呢？
Where are you at with the club?
或者我不应该问？
Or shouldn't I be asking?
有一个教父悖论
Godfather paradox.
越保持距离 就能越亲近
More distance I try to create, closer I get.
Jax很喜欢你 Nero
Jax loves you, Nero.
我能看出来
I see how he looks at you.
他会听你的
How he listens to you.
是啊 嗯..
Yeah, well...
可惜太大了 我不能收养
little too old to adopt.
你可以娶我啊
You can always marry me.
没有冒犯的意思 娃他妈
No offense, mama.
我知道你老公发生的事情
I've seen what happens to your husbands.
结局可不太美好
It ain't pretty.
是啊
No.
不太好
It's not.
有你走进我的生活 我太幸福了
I'm so glad you're in our lives.
是啊
Yeah.
我也是
Me, too.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
你们有什么需要？
What do you want?
能告诉我今天你在哪吗？
Can you tell us where you were today?
为什么/
Why?
Clay Morrow 没有被送到郡法院
Clay Morrow didn't make it to the county courthouse.
押运他的车中了埋伏
His transport was ambushed.
有8到9个不明身份的袭击者
Eight or nine unknown assailants.
他们杀害一个州警 伤了3个 其中两个伤势严重
They killed one of our sheriffs,
injured three-- two critically.
听说了 我很遗憾
I heard. I'm sorry.
那些待定的方案 现在已经取消了
Those other complications I had pending are now off the table,
这就是说 我决定接受与你的交易
which means I've decided to take you up on your offer.
换取你的合作 来对付帮会
In exchange for your cooperation against the MC,
你将会在Pamela Toric的谋杀案中得到豁免
you'll get immunity from Pamela Toric's murder.
我的孩子怎么说？还有保护措施
What about my boys? And protection.
如果你想获得证人保护计划 那就意味着要引用反黑法案了
If you want Witness Protection, it'll mean using RICO.
你要提供给我们的是重大犯罪事实
You'll have to provide us with a federal crime.
军火走私 敲诈勒索 谋杀
Gunrunning, extortion, murder.
告诉我们 谁把Clay截走的
Just tell us who broke out Clay.
我应该怎么做？
What would I have to do?
给我们无可辩驳的铁证
Provide us with irrefutable evidence.
如果我...
If I...
从一个帮会成员体内取出一颗今天劫持事件中的子弹
pulled a bullet out of a club member from today's shooting-
一个州警射出的子弹--
a sheriff's bullet--
上面会携带有DNA
it would have DNA on it.
那算是证据吗？
Would that be proof?
加上你的证词 那就是
With your testimony, yes,
那将证明 有一个帮会成员在犯罪现场
that would put the member at the crime scene,
从而证实混乱之子要为此事负责
prove the Sons were responsible.
我需要需要一些时间
I'm going to need more time.
多久？
- How much time?
至少要等到明天
- At least until tomorrow.
你只有这一次机会 医生
You only have one chance at this, Doctor.
我得走了 Gemma在外面等着我
I have to go. Gemma's waiting outside.
你怎么认为？
So, what do you think?
我认为她将忙碌一整夜
I think she's in for a very long night.
你要我们跟踪她吗？
Do you want me to tail her?
不 我们不能把她置于险地
No. We don't want to put her at risk.
我会打电话给司法部 看看能不能帮她争取到证人保护计划
I'll call up the DOJ, dig in about getting her WITSEC.
Galt分局接到到一个匿名举报
Galt division just followed up on an anonymous tip.
在104号公路的一个机库 发现4具尸体 6箱KG-9
Found four dead bodies and six cases
of KG-9's in a hangar off 104.
其中两具尸体 一个是Clay Morrow 另外一个是Gaalan O'Shay
Two of the DB's, Clay Morrow and Gaalan O'Shay.
看来今晚对于每个人 都是漫漫长夜
Looks like it's going to be a long night for everybody.

干得漂亮 医生
That was beautiful, Doc.
再取出一小块，他就脱离险境了
Just one more little piece, and he should be out of the woods.
她的白色折边帽哪去了？
"Where was her white frilled cap?
还有她的礼服和裙子
And her gown and petticoat?
她长得真是又小又黑
And how small she had grown, and how brown.
浑身长满了刺刺
And covered with prickles.
为什么  Tiggy-Winkle太太只是一个
Why, Mrs. Tiggy-Winkle was nothing but a..."
刺猬
- Hedgehog.
对了
- That's right.
刺猬
Hedgehog.
"But then how could she have
found three clean pocket handkins?"
为什么我们不....
Why don't we finish...
呃 不好意思
- Uh, sorry.
嗨
- Hey.
不是故意打断你们的讲故事时间
Didn't mean to disturb your story time.
来吧
Here you go.
奶奶
Grandma.
我会 呃 再去看一看Wendy 然后
I'll, uh, check on Wendy one more time, and...
然后我就告辞了
then I'm gonna split.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你 Wayne
Thank you, Wayne.
嗯
Yeah.
晚安
Good night.
嗨 宝贝
Hey, baby.
嗨
Hey.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
嗨
Hey.
欢迎回来 Bobby
Welcome back, Bobby.
Teller兑现了她的承诺
Teller kept his promise.
把Gaalan和枪支都交给了你
Gave you Gaalan and the guns.
不 他没有
No, he didn't.
我的协议里可没有包括一摞尸体
The deal I made didn't include a stack of dead bodies.
我知道 今天你大可不必帮这个忙
I know you didn't have to help us today.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我很高心 他不会有事了
I'm just glad he's going to be okay.
我明白了...
I understand...
你那样做的原因
why you did everything you did.
对不起 都是因为和我在一起 才把你变成这样
I'm sorry being with me took you to that place.
原创翻译 倾情奉献
英文字幕：n17t01 翻译：Wilsonyy 校对：Dena